offerdaddy.com 2019-03-07

# OfferDaddy - Offers & Surveys only Wall for Mobile and Web Apps

**Effective date: May 10, 2018**

OfferDaddy.com offers walls (both web and SDK for mobile apps) ("us", "we", or "our") operates the https://www.offerdaddy.com offers walls and the OfferDaddy Android and iOS SDK for mobile application (the "Service").

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data.

We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions.

### Definitions

#### Personal Data

Personal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession).

#### Usage Data

Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).

#### Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of data stored on a User’s device.

#### Data Controller

Data Controller means a person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal data are, or are to be, processed.

For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your data.

#### Data Processor (or Service Providers)

Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any person (other than an employee of the Data Controller) who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller.

We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data more effectively.

#### Data Subject

Data Subject is any living individual who is the subject of Personal Data.

#### User

The User is the individual using our Service. The User corresponds to the Data Subject, who is the subject of Personal Data.

### Information: Collection and Use

We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.

### Types of Data Collected

#### Personal Data

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Data"). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:

  * Email address
  * First and last name
  * Phone number
  * Cookies and Usage Data

We may use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send.

#### Usage Data

We may also collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service or when you access the Service by or through a mobile device ("Usage Data").

This Usage Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

When you access the Service by or through a mobile device, this Usage Data may include information such as the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device unique ID, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browser you use, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

#### Tracking & Cookies Data

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.

Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

#### Examples of Cookies we use:

**Session Cookies.** We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.

Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.

Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.

### Use of Data

We uses the collected data for various purposes:

  * To provide and maintain our Service
  * To notify you about changes to our Service
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so
  * To provide customer support
  * To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Service
  * To monitor the usage of our Service
  * To detect, prevent and address technical issues
  * To provide you with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless you have opted not to receive such information

### Retention of Data

We will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.

We will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.

### Transfer Of Data

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside Uruguay and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to Uruguay and process it there. As well, we store and process data at other locations such as United States and to offer a better and faster Service we may also store and process data at other locations around the world (replicated data).

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.

### Disclosure Of Data

#### Disclosure for Law Enforcement

Under certain circumstances, we may be required to disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).

#### Legal Requirements

We may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  * To comply with a legal obligation
  * To protect and defend the rights or property of OfferDaddy.com offers walls (both web and SDK for mobile apps)
  * To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
  * To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
  * To protect against legal liability

### Security of Data

The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### "Do Not Track" Signals

We do not support Do Not Track ("DNT"). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.

You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.

### Your Rights

We aim to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.

Whenever made possible, you can update your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to change your Personal Data, please contact us to make the required changes.

If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us at privacy@offerdaddy.com

In certain circumstances, you have the right:

  * To access and receive a copy of the Personal Data we hold about you
  * To rectify any Personal Data held about you that is inaccurate
  * To request the deletion of Personal Data held about you

You have the right to data portability for the information you provide to us. You can request to obtain a copy of your Personal Data in a commonly used electronic format so that you can manage and move it.

**Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.**

### Service Providers

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service ("Service Providers"), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

#### Analytics

We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.

#### Google Analytics

Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: <http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>

### Links To Other Sites

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on any of our offers or surveys, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

### Children's Privacy

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 ("Children").

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

### Changes To This Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the "effective date" at the top of this Privacy Policy.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

## Information Security Policy

### 1\. Purpose, scope and users

The aim of this top-level Policy is to define the purpose, direction, principles and basic rules for information security management.

This Policy is applied to the entire Information Security Management System (ISMS), as defined in the ISMS Scope Document.

Users of this document are all employees of OfferDaddy.com, as well as relevant external parties.

### 2\. Reference documents

  * ISO/IEC 27001 standard, clauses 5.2 and 5.3
  * ISMS Scope Document
  * Previous section of this Privacy Policy

### 3\. Basic information security terminology

**Confidentiality** – characteristic of the information by which it is available only to authorized persons or systems.

**Integrity** – characteristic of the information by which it is changed only by authorized persons or systems in an allowed way.

**Availability** – characteristic of the information by which it can be accessed by authorized persons when it is needed.

**Information security** – preservation of confidentiality, integrity and availability of information.

**Information Security Management System** – part of overall management processes that takes care of planning, implementing, maintaining, reviewing, and improving the information security. 

### 4\. Managing the information security 

#### 4.1. Objectives and measurement

General objectives for the information security management system are the following: creating a better market image, reducing the damage caused by potential incidents, user satisfaction and proper serving of users of our platform(s); goals are in line with the organization's business objectives, strategy and business plans. OfferDaddy.com’s Director is responsible for reviewing these general ISMS objectives and setting new ones.

Objectives for individual security controls or groups of controls are proposed by the Director of OfferDaddy.com and his Assistants, support employees, development team in rare occassions, business development staff and account managers, and approved by OfferDaddy.com’s Director in the Statement of Applicability.

All the objectives must be reviewed at least once a year.

OfferDaddy.com will measure the fulfillment of all the objectives.

OfferDaddy.com’s Director is responsible for setting the method for measuring the achievement of the objectives – the measurement will be performed at least once a year and OfferDaddy.com’s assistants will analyze and evaluate the measurement results and report them to OfferDaddy.com’s Director as input materials for the Management review.

#### 4.2. Information security requirements

This Policy and the entire ISMS must be compliant with legal and regulatory requirements relevant to the organization in the field of information security, as well as with contractual obligations, data secrecy, personal data protection of OfferDaddy.com's publishers and their users.

#### 4.3. Information security controls

The process of selecting the controls (safeguards) is defined in the Risk Assessment and Risk Treatment Methodology.

#### 4.4. Responsibilities

Responsibilities for the ISMS are the following:

  * OfferDaddy.com’s Director is responsible for ensuring that the ISMS is implemented and maintained according to this Policy, and for ensuring all necessary resources are available
  * OfferDaddy.com’s Director is responsible for operational coordination of the ISMS as well as for reporting about the performance of the ISMS
  * OfferDaddy.com’s internal process assistants must review the ISMS at least once a year or each time a significant change occurs, and prepare minutes from that meeting. The purpose of the management review is to establish the suitability, adequacy and effectiveness of the ISMS.
  * OfferDaddy.com’s Director will implement information security training and awareness programs for employees
  * the protection of integrity, availability, and confidentiality of assets is the responsibility of the owner of each asset 
  * all security incidents or weaknesses must be reported to OfferDaddy’s Director
  * OfferDaddy.com’s Director will define which information related to information security will be communicated to which interested party (both internal and external), by whom and when
  * OfferDaddy.com’s Director is responsible for adopting and implementing the Training and Awareness Plan, which applies to all persons who have a role in information security management 

#### 4.5. Policy communication

The Director has to ensure that all employees of OfferDaddy.com, as well as appropriate external parties are familiar with this Policy.

### 5\. Support for ISMS implementation

Hereby the OfferDaddy.com’s Director declares that ISMS implementation and continual improvement will be supported with adequate resources in order to achieve all objectives set in this Policy, as well as satisfy all identified requirements.

### 6\. Validity and document management

This document is valid as of May 10, 2018.

The owner of this document is OfferDaddy.com’s Director, who must check and, if necessary, update the document at least once a year.

When evaluating the effectiveness and adequacy of this document, the following criteria need to be considered:

  * number of employees and external parties who have a role in the ISMS, but are not familiar with this document
  * non-compliance of the ISMS with the laws and regulations, contractual obligations, and other internal documents of the organization
  * ineffectiveness of ISMS implementation and maintenance
  * unclear responsibilities for ISMS implementation

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us: privacy@offerdaddy.com
